Join Tata AIA Life Insurance Business.  Is
a housewife meant only to manage the house
or
can she build her future along with the house?  Hello friends,
I am Yogendra Verma, Recruitment
Manager Tata AIA and today I am going to talk to you about
a great opportunity especially for housewives and ladies empowerment.
Why is business perfect for housewives?  See, a housewife has
great skills.  Number one relationship
management.  Number two is patience, number three is
trust building, number four is
understanding family responsibilities.  And these
qualities are
most important to become a successful life insurance advisor.  Just
think, when you think so much about the security of your home, then
you can also help in the security of others' homes.  Isn't it
?  Let's talk about why choose Tata AIA?
Now the question arises, if you want to do insurance business then
why Tata AIA?  Because friends, the
name Tata itself is the identity of the trust.  Tata
AIA is the second largest private
life insurance company in India.  This
is the company producing the highest MDRT.
And look at the power of the products here.
Here, term plan is the biggest need of every family
and is
available at very reasonable pricing.
You will find the best ULIP plans here, which
can help you build wealth and protection, and there are
plenty of guaranteed savings and assured plans,
which are amazing.  Retirement
solutions are also genuinely available here to secure your future.  The
scope of life insurance is so vast that it is needed in every household.
How much income can a housewife make
?  Now the biggest question is how much will the income be?
Friends, this is not a job but a salary, there is
no salary of any kind here.  This is a commission based
business opportunity in which the more
policies you sell, the more your income will
increase.  The commission here will be from 21% to 45%.
Even housewives can easily join here part time and
can easily earn Rs 25,000 to Rs 500 per month and if
you are serious then you can become MDRT here and
earn Rs 13 lakh annually.
MDRT stands for Million Dollar Round Table.
This is the
biggest reward and award in life insurance which is USA
recognized and many
women are working on it and earning good money.
You will also get some extra benefits
here.  Along with this you will
get monthly and quarterly contests.
Domestic and international fully paid
trips will be provided by the company.  In which
you can do world tour.  You
can visit multiple countries.  You will get
lifetime free training and
learning support at company expense.  And most importantly,
you will not be left alone.  Three to
four managers will always support you
so that you can build a professional life. So let's talk about
what is the mandatory process here
?  So the process is very simple.  There
is one mandatory exam here, the fee for which will be ₹850.
Anyone can apply all over India.
The exam will be held at a centre near you.  You will have to take two
days of full day compulsory physical branch
training.
This is mandatory before the exam.  And there will be objective type
question answers.  There will be questions of 50 marks.
Passing marks must be 15 marks.
You will have to prepare a list of 50 prospects before the exam.
50 people and has a 100% digital training
platform.  Training will be available from 9:30 am to 10:30 am,
Monday to Saturday.
Training will be available from 8 to 9 in the evening.  5 to 10
sessions will be available in a month.  After getting the code, it
is necessary to take one policy in the first month
with a premium of Rs 400 and it will be necessary to take 12 policies in a year
so that your code remains active.  Let me
talk about women empowerment,
friends, the mission of developed India is India's
dream, developed India in 2047 and the agenda
is insurance for every house, so think if women do
not come forward then how will every house be secure,
this business not only gives income, it
also gives respect, confidence and empowerment
which is amazing and useful for you.
If you also
want to create your identity and financial freedom by being a housewife.
Why is it the biggest upgrade?  If you are a
network marketer, MLM leader then
I have brought Amazing Working for you.
You have formed your team but is the
income permanent?  Join Tata where the
Tata name and 99.13%
claim ratio will keep your team on its toes.
Recruit your team in Tata AA leadership model and earn unlimited profits.  5%
to 30% is real business.  There
is no hassle in making any member.  Exam fee will be ₹850
and registration fee will be ₹5000.
Free International Trips with Tata where
you can create history.  Only full time
working is available.  Two days of branch
training is mandatory.  Long term vision
is important for you and you have leadership skills.
You can form a team.  Can trend people.
So don't delay.  Write on WhatsApp
Tata AIA Leader, I
will genuinely guide you, leave MLM,
become a corporate leader of Tata and build your future.
Hello, the whole world is
looking towards India today.  Our country is on its way to
becoming the third largest economy in the world.
But do you know which sector is the
brightest star of this Indian growth story
?  So that is the health
insurance sector.  Even today,
70% of India's population does not have proper health insurance
cover.  Just imagine, where the demand is so
high and the supply is so low,
how much scope is there for business?  Are you still
chasing old jobs or
want to be a part of a sector that is going to
grow like a rocket for the next 20 years
?  So hello, I am Yogendra Verma,
Recruitment Manager.  I am helping over 500
partners take advantage of this historic booming
sector.
To take advantage of this boom in the health sector, you will need the country's most
trusted company ICC LB.  We are the
number one general insurance company in the country.
When the country grows, the leader will grow first.   The
use of Artificial Intelligence in claim settlement and 100% digital model
puts us far ahead of others.  Along with
15% to 35% commission on selling health insurance,
there is also a sea of ​​passive income like 15% renewal
commission which can
make you successful for generations to come.  Here
you get not only money but also respect and the opportunity for international paid trips.  There are
strict rules for success.
Great work requires discipline for great success.  There are
some
clear conditions to join us.  Before getting into the license code,
you will need to create a prospecting list of 50 people from your network.   No
war is won without preparation.
After getting the code, it will be necessary to take a
health policy of Rs 15,000 premium in the first month so
that your code becomes active
and it is necessary to take 12 policies in a year
so that your code continues.  Your
qualification should be at least 12th
and if your age is between 20 years to 65 years
then you are welcome.  It is mandatory to give the exam here
and the fee for it is
₹1000 and it takes 10 to 12 days for the exam to come, for which
my team will guide you.
India is changing.  Are you
ready to change your destiny?  The sector is growing
, the country is growing.  You will
not be left as a mere spectator, will you?  Join ICC LB
and become a shareholder in India's progress.
If you
want to secure and prosper your future by joining the mission of Developed India 2047, then WhatsApp your name
and IC Lobard Health Agent now.
WhatsApp number is 859540
7616. Please like, share and follow the channel
so that you keep getting better updates.  Hello
Hello Friends, Next Video is
named as Motor Insurance Agents Why
Become Tata AIA Life Insurance Agent?  So let's
talk about being a motor insurance agent and let me
ask you a question.  If you
insure a vehicle, have you ever
thought of insuring a human life?
Hello friends, I am Yogendra Verma,
Recruitment Manager Tata AI.  Today's
video is especially for those motor insurance agents
who want to take their business to the next level.
Friends, look at the biggest reality of motor insurance business, motor
insurance is necessary.  But listen to the punch line.  The
car is renewed once a year.
But the impact of life insurance
lasts for the whole life.  The
complexity in motor insurance is very high.
But the premium is also limited.  And the client
's focus remains only on the price.
Make it cheaper brother.  But life insurance is a
trust based business.  This is the amazing
business of future planning.
Why is an upgrade from Motor to Life necessary?
You already have clients, car owners
, business owners, working
professionals, female families.  Now
imagine all of them need a term life term plan.  There
is a risk of car accident.
But the risk to the family's future is the
biggest risk.  Term insurance is a
basic need of every person.  Why is Tata AIA the
brand you trust?  Let's talk about this also.
Many people have a
question in their mind that
why should they join Tata AIA in life insurance?  So its
very simple answer is Tata is equal to
trust.  Tata AIA is the
second largest private life insurance
company in India.  Highest MDRT
is one of the leading producer companies.  And the
products are such that the client automatically
says that I want Tata products.  Be it a
term plan which is the
need of every family.  Be it guaranteed assured
plans that provide fixed security
or ULIP plans that are a
great combo of wealth plus protection and
what to say about retirement planning,
pension ready solutions are available here.
ULIP equal to SIP plus
insurance is a jackpot for motor agents.
Now know the biggest advantage: Motor
clients are already financially aware.
You can now offer them.
ULIP offers SIP like investment option,
mutual fund style wealth creation along with
life cover protection and in this single plan
you get investment insurance plus
future security, that is,
this upgrade becomes super powerful for motor agents
and from here a second source of
earning starts.  You can do this
work in an easily flexible manner in both part time and full time
options.
In which there is no challenge of any kind.
Whether you do it part time or
full time.  Later on,
you can manage it as a career full time.
You will keep learning here and earning will also
start and continue.  This is amazing
amazing working.  Here
you will get higher commission plus higher income.  Please pay attention.  Let me
first tell you how you will earn here.  This is not any kind of job.  There is
no salary of any kind available here.
This is a commission based business opportunity.
Your income will depend on the number of policies you sell.  The commission ranges from 21%
to 45%.  It is possible in part time
and can also be done in full time.
You can earn a minimum of Rs 25,000 to Rs 500 per
month here and in future, it is possible to earn Rs 2 lakh, Rs 5 lakh, Rs
10 lakh per month.  By
becoming an MDRT, one can earn ₹13 lakh annually here
and MDRT
is famous for Tata MDRT culture.
Most of the MDRTs are manufactured within Tata companies.
And you will enjoy it even more after hearing about the extra benefits.
Here
you will find monthly and quarterly contests in which
you can qualify for domestic and international trips
in fully paid versions.
You will get lifetime free trainings and learning support here.  You will always have three to four managers to
guide you.  You are
not alone here.  The entire ecosystem
works with you here.  There are just
some mandatory procedures here.  You will need to
share your basic KYC documents with us.
Which I will share with you the list of
documents.  In the process, you will have to appear for
an exam which is mandatory and the
fee for it will be ₹850.
You can apply for this at the all India level, wherever you are.
The exam will be held at the nearest centre.
You will have to take two days of full day compulsory training.
In the local near by branch in which we
will align and here 50 questions will
come out of which you have to pass 15.  It will be
necessary to get 15 marks.
Before the exam, it will be
necessary to prepare a prospecting list of 50 people
so that after the exam, work can be done on
what I and my team will teach you.   It is a
100% digital training platform.  Here the
training is held in the morning
from 9:30 am to 10:30 am Monday to Saturday
through Microsoft Teams.  Training takes place in the evening
through ZM Meeting from 8
to 9. You will get 5 to 10 training sessions
in the evening only.  After receiving the code, it will be
necessary to make a policy in the first month.   It is
mandatory to have a premium of Rs 400 and 12 policies in a year to keep your code
running.  So let me ask you the final question.
As a motor insurance agent, will you limit yourself to just vehicles
or will you also provide lifetime wealth protection to your clients?
This is an opportunity to
capture the term plan market.   There
is an opportunity to create ULIP wealth
and move ahead in the retirement planning segment.
You can get higher commission plus tips
here.  Better Future
Prospective can be yours here.
So if you want to become a motor insurance agent and
make it your next income pillar, then
you have to WhatsApp me.  Tata AIA
Agent my WhatsApp number is 981826521
or write BOP in DM.  BOP
stands for Business Opportunity Presentation.
I will share its complete PDF with you
on WhatsApp by writing in DM.  And I
am Yogendra Verma Recruitment Manager
Tata AIA.  500 plus advisors are already
working on all over India basis.
So please like, share
and follow the channel so that you keep getting updates.
I am talking to you only.   Are
you still flying the flag of the same company
and surviving on low commissions?
Do you know that you can sell
all the insurance companies and all the mutual
funds in India from a single platform.
That too without leaving any old agency.
Yes friends, you will not believe it
but it is possible.  Hello, I am
Yogendra Verma, Recruitment Manager, Bajaj
Capital.  Today, 5000 plus agents from India and abroad are
joining me and creating history.
Bajaj Capital gives you a super
platform where you can buy all the companies like Life, Health, Motor and
Travel
Insurance along with Mutual Funds
together on a single platform.  And the biggest thing is that
you will get the guarantee of highest commission and best trail commission in mutual funds here.
Which can be a win-win situation for you.
Those who have come to the channel for the first time,
please follow it.  Otherwise this
important deal will be missed.  It
is very important.  If you
are a fresher in the insurance industry then
POS code will be generated for you, no exam, no fees
, same day code will be generated and you
can start working in 3 days.  And if you are already an
experienced agent, an
agent of any IIT company or
already have a licensed POS code from any broker,
then the marketing code is available for you here.
In which there will be no exam or any
fee.  Same day code will be generated and
you can start working after 3 days.  Even if you
already have an IIDA code or broker
code, you can still join Bajaj Capital and
earn extra through marketing code.
No worries, it is 100%
legal.  You will not face any kind of challenge or
problem.  If I talk about Bajaj
Capital, we have the trust of 60 years and
1000 plus offices. Our platform is 100%
digital.  If your customer has a Bajaj
Capital consumer card, he
can purchase any policy on instant EMI.
And now listen to the topic of earnings.
How much income are you going to get from where?  If I
talk about life insurance, you can take commission from 25% to 40% to 45%.  If I
talk to health insurance then you can get 15% to 35%
commission.  And
you will also get a good commission on portability here.  If we
talk about model insurance,
you will get commission ranging from 2% to 75%.  In this
you can do two wheeler, three wheeler, four wheeler, commercial everything.  Talking about SMA and
Group Insurance,
you can get a payout of 5% to 15% and up to 30% here.
Talking about travel insurance in SMA business,
you can get a payout of 20% to 40%.
You are going to get amazing working here.
Not just sales, we provide amazing
claim support and most accurate timely payouts.
We know what your hard work is worth.
Whether you are in India or an NRI,
start your financial journey today.  Do
n't be part of the crowd.  Become a brand yourself.   Don't
delay with Bajaj Capital.  This
opportunity is available for a limited time.  Now
call or WhatsApp the number given on the screen.
Write Bajaj
Capital Agent Code on WhatsApp.  If you want to get POS code
then write the POS code.  If you want to get the marketing code, then
write the marketing code and it is going to be
destroyed for you.  Don't delay.
Get your code today.  Hello, blessed